priceblink.com 2017-09-20

# PriceBlink:: Privacy Policy

**PriceBlink Privacy Policy  
**   
**Last Updated:   June 16, 2014**   
**General**   
This is the Privacy Policy of PriceBlink ("us", or "we").  By accessing the PriceBlink.com website or using the PriceBlink add-on (collectively known as "PriceBlink"), you agree that you have read and understand the following privacy policy, which describes how we use your personal information, and what options you have to make changes to or request the deletion of information submitted to us via the PriceBlink service.  

Please read the Terms of Use and this Privacy Policy carefully. Our Terms of Use and Privacy Policy may be modified by us from time to time, and will become effective immediately upon posting to PriceBlink.com.  It is your responsibility to regularly check PriceBlink.com to determine if there have been changes to the Terms of Use or the Privacy Policy and to review the changes.  If you do not agree with either the Terms of Use or this Privacy Policy, do not use the PriceBlink.com website or the PriceBlink add-on.

**No Use Of PriceBlink By Persons Under The Age Of 13**

The PriceBlink service is not intended for use by anyone under 18, except with the explicit permission and under the supervision of a parent or guardian who accepts full legal responsibility for the minor's use.  PriceBlink does not knowingly collect or use personally identifiable information from children under 13. If a child under 13 has provided us with personally identifiable information without parental or guardian consent, the parent or guardian should contact us to remove the minor's information.

**What information does PriceBlink collect?**

PriceBlink collects two types of data:  1) User Submitted Data, and 2) Passive Data.

 _User Submitted Data_

PriceBlink collects personal information that you provide to us for the purposes of site updates, newsletters, notifications, and additional PriceBlink functionalities.   Examples of User Submitted Data that you have the option of providing might include email, zip code, phone numbers.  We will not use this data to provide any services or marketing that you have not requested.  We may share User Submitted Data with persons we employ directly, or as contractors or agents at our direction, for purposes of administering our business activities, or providing customer services such as support.

**_You are not required to provide any User Submitted Data to use PriceBlink._** _  _By providing additional information, PriceBlink might be able to provide additional functionality to users, but there is no requirement that users provide personal information to use PriceBlink.

 _  
Passive Data_

PriceBlink Add-on

When you use your browser to navigate the web, the PriceBlink add-on enables you to find additional pricing and coupon information.  In order to provide these services the PriceBlink add-on collects the following information: the characteristics of the item, the retailer page, the url of the page you are on, and other anonymous technical data such as IP address.

Cookies

PriceBlink utilizes an industry standard technology called "cookies" to collect information about how PriceBlink is used. Passive Data collected may include your browser type, operating system, ISP, the date / time of visits, PriceBlink.com pages viewed, and the referring site to PriceBlink.com and any third party site PriceBlink links to. Passive Data is collected on an aggregate basis without any association to your personal information so that you remain anonymous.

We may also allow third parties, such as advertisers on our PriceBlink, to place cookies on PriceBlink in order to improve your online experience after you leave PriceBlink. The third party cookies used on PriceBlink are designed to improve your online experience by facilitating the receipt of targeted advertisements while on PriceBlink and while you are viewing other websites. These third parties may use information about your visits to PriceBlink and other web sites obtained through their cookie only to provide advertisements for goods and services of interest to you. Other companies' use of these cookies is subject to their own privacy policies and not ours.  **_We do not provide these third parties with any personally identifiable information_** _._

Clicking on links to third party sites within the PriceBlink extension will, in many cases, route the user via an affiliate network.  In such cases, affiliate cookies may be used.

If you do not wish to transmit cookie information about yourself, you may choose to turn off the cookie function in your web browser.  If you do choose to turn off cookies, certain features of PriceBlink might be affected and not work properly.

**How PriceBlink Uses The Information Collected**

PriceBlink uses the User Submitted Data collected to deliver the content, features, notifications, and services that you have requested.   **_You are not required to provide any User Submitted Data to use PriceBlink, however we do not guarantee that all features of the PriceBlink service will work properly without User Submitted Data.   _**We will not use the information you provide to send unsolicited marketing to you.  The purpose of collecting User Submitted Data is to make additional features, information and services available to you.  PriceBlink shall give users the option to remove themselves from any further messaging at any time by contacting us.  

If you contact us via email, we may retain the information included the original email, along with any response to your email, in order to facilitate future customer support.  We will not use this information to contact you for any other purpose.

If a user elects to use our "Share this Page" referral service for informing another user PriceBlink, we ask for both the users name and email and the recipient's name and email.  We will automatically send the recipient a one-time email inviting them to visit PriceBlink.com.  Subsequent to transmission, both the user's and the recipient's information shall be deleted.

Passive Data shall be used to optimize the performance, improve the usability, or enhance the experience on PriceBlink.com and the PriceBlink add-on.  We may share with third parties, such as advertisers, other website operators or data research companies, information about site usage, demographics or other characteristics.  Any data shared shall be anonymous, and not contain user personally identifiable information.

We may use data collected to manage PriceBlink service, help diagnose problems with servers, and optimize the design of the PriceBlink service.

**Links to Third Party Websites**

PriceBlink is a directory of offers at third party sites.  You will be transferred to online merchants or other third party sites through links on PriceBlink.  PriceBlink is not responsible for the content or privacy practices of those sites, and our Privacy Policy does not apply to information collected by those sites.  Before using third party sites, you should read and understand those sites' privacy policies to ensure you agree to their terms.

**Sharing Information with the Government or As Otherwise Required by Law**

We may disclose information when we believe in good faith that the law requires it, or if we consider it necessary to maintain service and improve our products and services.  
**  
Sale or Transfer of Information**   
In the event of a sale, merger, liquidation, dissolution, or transfer of the PriceBlink business or assets, all information collected may be sold, assigned, or transferred to the acquiring party. Should you object to the transfer of your User Submitted Information, you have the option to have your User Submitted Information removed from our database.    
**Security**   
PriceBlink has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of the data under our control.  Although we take reasonable steps to safeguard your personally identifiable information, we can not be responsible for the acts of those who gain unauthorized access, and we make no warranty, express, implied or otherwise, that we will prevent such access.   
**Opt Out / Removal of User Submitted Information**   
PriceBlink provides users the opportunity to opt-out of receiving communications from us and our partners at the point where we request User Submitted Information from you.   
You may also request that we remove your User Submitted Information from our database, or stop sending you future communications by [contacting us](mailto:contact@priceblink.com?body=%0A%0A%0A%0A%0A%0AIf%20you%20are%20reporting%20a%20technical%20problem,%20the%20following%20information%20will%20assist%20our%20troubleshooting:%0A34.207.98.73%0AMozilla/5.0%20\(X11;%20Linux%20x86_64\)%20AppleWebKit/537.36%20\(KHTML,%20like%20Gecko\)%20HeadlessChrome/69.0.3494.0%20Safari/537.36).    
**Corrections**   
Users may submit requests to PriceBlink for changing, deleting, and modifying User Submitted Information, by [contacting us](mailto:contact@priceblink.com?body=%0A%0A%0A%0A%0A%0AIf%20you%20are%20reporting%20a%20technical%20problem,%20the%20following%20information%20will%20assist%20our%20troubleshooting:%0A34.207.98.73%0AMozilla/5.0%20\(X11;%20Linux%20x86_64\)%20AppleWebKit/537.36%20\(KHTML,%20like%20Gecko\)%20HeadlessChrome/69.0.3494.0%20Safari/537.36).
